[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ soft emotional song playing]
[breathing shakily]
But why would you say liking me
is being greedy?
Because you'll go back soon?
It doesn't matter if I'm being greedy now.
I can't stop my feelings anyway.
So I'll just keep going,
because I don't want
to waste our time together.
Then don't say
you're being greedy anymore.
If you say that again,
I won't let it slide.
I should be careful, then.
[chuckles softly]
[♪ song fades]
EPISODE 8
Stop staring at it.
It won't even be visible tomorrow.
Oh. And make sure to call your grandma.
She'll be worried sick
after you left like that.
[inhales sharply] I will.
I used to be just like that watch.
I was frozen in time,
but someone made time move again for me.
Like this.
So how about letting time with your dad
start moving again?
The past is the past.
What's important
is the time that will flow from now on.
[♪ pleasant music playing]
[Nana] Her boyfriend died back then.
He went to study in Boston,
but he suddenly died.
Hey, roomie.
[Chan] The fact that I lived
while he died from that accident…
It's a good thing you took it out.
I want someone to have joy in their life.
She was a grateful disruption
that made me live again.
Mr. Park, we…
Of course. I know.
Take her home safely.
Let's go, Genius.
Go on in.
Bye.
[♪ music fades]
[Haran stutters] Look forward.
It'll be dangerous
if you fall down the hill.
[♪ pleasant music continues]
[sighs] I'm relieved.
You're warm.
It's just that…
this feels like a dream.
I can't believe it.
-Should I make this feel more real?
-[grunts]
No, thanks.
[both laugh]
[sighs] I'll go now. Head inside.
Get back safely.
[♪ music ends]
What a relief.
[grunts]
[groans]
-[groans softly]
-[door opens]
[Chan] Now, now.
You didn't take your meds again? [grunts]
-I told you to take them on time.
-[sighs]
Let's go to the hospital this week.
Keep your cardiac enzyme
test results in your wallet
so someone can see it if you ever collapse
when you're not with me.
We have to go, okay?
Just think of me as a nagging son,
and come with me.
All right.
And you
should think of me
as a father who listens to you,
so tell me anything
that you have a hard time
telling anyone else.
You can tell me
anything that troubles you.
I'll be your safe space.
I wasn't trying to hide
my relationship with Ms. Song…
You really like her, right?
[sighs softly]
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
-Yes.
-All right.
Let her feel joy again.
You don't need a reason
to want someone to be happy.
As long as you're sincere, it's okay.
[deliveryman] Ms. Song,
there's an international delivery.
[Haran] Wow.
I finally got the sketch sample
for my design.
Make some noise!
It's all thanks to this pen.
But how did you come up
with the idea of sending me a pen?
[Chan] I kept thinking about how you said
you felt like you were trapped.
I used to feel that way, too.
Back then, I kept thinking the same thing.
If…
there was just a small crack
to breathe through, I could live.
But…
that "if" never came true for me.
I guess I wanted
that pen to be that "if" for you.
[sighs]
Chan understands me so well…
[Chan] Sorry, I was rambling.
I should go now.
[♪ music fades]
-[Ben] Great work today.
-[Chan] You too.
-I'm going back to Korea first.
-Okay, sure.
[Ben chuckles]
[chuckles, inhales sharply]
[sighs]
[Haran] Maybe it's because I lost
the pen I used for seven years,
but I couldn't sketch anything
during the two days here.
[Chan in English]
Yes, seven years ago. Early July.
And the engraving is Haran.
[shop owner] One second.
Uh, yeah. We have the model name
and the engraving design on file.
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
[Haran sighs]
[in Korean] The past is the past.
What's important…
[Chan and Haran] is the time
that will flow from now on.
[wind whooshing]
-[leaves rustling]
-[birds chirping]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[Hayeong] Grandma.
[♪ music fades]
Where have you been?
I was at a meeting.
Our dinner ended late.
A meeting dressed like this?
And what's this…
I'll do it.
I'm tired. I'm going to bed.
Grandma, did you go to Seongsu…
I'm sorry, but just let this go for now.
Please.
What?
I just…
thought we haven't been
talking much lately.
Are you sure nothing's wrong?
What's wrong is you asking questions
when I'm so sleepy.
-[chuckles]
-Go to bed.
All right. Good night.
[♪ pensive music playing]
Why are her shoes like that?
It couldn't have been a meeting.
Where in the world was she?
[sighs wearily]
EXAMINATION
[♪ music fades]
[automation] The door is closing.
[exclaims] Let me get on!
Thank you.
[Hayeong panting]
-[exclaims softly]
-[clears throat]
[Hayeong] What's that?
He's the definition of neatness,
and he's got bedhead?
[in English] Okay,
I'll check and email you.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[in Korean]
He's late and has bedhead? Mr. Yeon?
What's going on?
That doesn't suit him at all.
[♪ music fades]
-Look. Isn't it crazy?
-[Sol and Raemee exclaim]
-This is insane.
-Is this for real?
Sorry! What are you up to?
Hayeong! Seunggyu took a rare photo.
What photo?
[Seunggyu] I was organizing the photos
I took during my trend research…
[exclaims] and I was shocked.
That stiff, uptight Mr. Yeon is dating?
-This is crazy!
-[Sol and Raemee giggle]
[Sol exclaims delightedly]
But they look so good together.
[Raemee] They do.
-[♪ amusing music playing]
-[folders thud loudly]
How shameless.
Why is she being so loud when she's late?
Hey, look.
She's the head of La Mode Eclat,
-and that's the co-head and her husband.
-[♪ music ends]
-[Sol groans]
-[Raemee] Oh, geez.
Seunggyu! They were just having
a business meeting.
[sighs] So they were the heads
of La Mode Eclat.
[Seunggyu laughs]
-Sorry about that.
-[whistling]
Oh, dear. Why is she suddenly whistling?
There's no in-between with her.
-[Sol chuckles softly]
-[stops whistling]
He's right.
Why am I relieved?
[Seunggyu] But I wonder if Mr. Yeon
would still have that default expression
when he's dating.
[Sol] No way. I'm sure he'll be different.
[inhales sharply] He might be
really sweet to the woman he likes.
[in English] Sweet?
[♪ enchanting music playing]
[in Korean] Your hand.
[Taeseok] You might slip
since you're wearing heels.
-[♪ enchanting music continuing]
-This happened to my friend,
uh…
but this guy
brushed off dry leaves in the dirt
with his bare hands so she wouldn't slip.
What does that mean?
With his bare hands?
That's love.
[stutters] Love?
Then if the woman cried,
and he looked at her with pity
and wiped her tears with his hand,
what does that mean?
[exclaims softly]
[softly] Love.
-[Hayeong gasps] He loves me?
-[♪ amusing music playing]
And the fact that
you're overanalyzing his every move
means you like him too.
-[all exclaim teasingly]
-No, that wasn't about me.
That was my friend.
-It's obvious it was about you.
-[laughs]
My friend told me during a school reunion.
[Sol] You liar.
Ms. Song Hayeong.
-The new material you mentioned…
-[Hayeong] Ah.
Uh… Mmm…
Hello?
Yes, hello.
-I just got an urgent call.
-[♪ music ends]
Are you busy right now?
I'm busy too.
[birds chirping]
What should I say when I give this to her?
Hmm? [chuckles softly]
Hey, you said
you're coming in the evening.
I'm meeting someone here.
Goodness.
You mean with me?
[footsteps approaching rapidly]
-She's meeting me!
-[Chan groans]
-Hmm?
-What? This is so sudden.
Something came up,
so she's returning to Mungyeong today.
Wow. You were going to meet without me?
-You're always leaving me out.
-[Chan's grandma] Right.
[Chan sighs, mumbles playfully]
-He's sulking.
-[chuckles]
This place looks nice.
Wow.
It's shattered and cracked.
And there seem to be
some pieces missing. Hmm?
Will it be too hard?
[sighs dejectedly]
I can make it work.
-[♪ lighthearted music playing]
-[exclaims]
It may take some time,
but as long as we don't give up,
it can be fixed somehow.
[sighs in relief]
[Chan's grandma]
It would be different from the original,
but let's think of it
as making it stronger.
Thank you so much.
Here's your coffee.
[Chan's grandma chuckles]
My grandson must be troubling you a lot.
If he does anything to irritate you,
you can just smack him on the back
and kick him out.
Really?
He's been nagging me so much lately
that I've been thinking about it.
I will keep that in mind.
[all laugh]
-Stop it.
-[Chan clears throat]
You must be curious about the house.
You can take a look after you're done.
No, it's your private space. I shouldn't…
It's fine. It's also Chan's house.
Give her a tour later.
Seeing you stay with someone so nice
makes me feel at ease.
[Chan's grandma chuckles]
Be good to him, all right?
I will.
[♪ music fades]
Wow. [chuckling]
[gasps]
So how about letting time with your dad
start moving again?
Chan.
[stutters] It's nothing. Never mind.
[in singsong] It was nothing. [chuckles]
-When will you visit again?
-[both chuckle]
That little brat isn't even seeing me off.
I should give him a smack.
[Chan] Grandma.
Can you drop me off on the way?
Where?
Daejeon.
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
I don't know what I'll do there,
but I think
I should at least give this back to him.
[Chan] Mm.
[chuckling]
[Chan's grandma exclaims softly]
[♪ music fades]
[Hadam's friend]
I saw Yougyum this weekend.
He was going to karaoke with his friends.
[Hadam] Are you having
a lot of fun these days?
Did you have fun at karaoke?
What? I…
[♪ amusing music playing]
Yeah, I had fun.
You seemed to be having fun, too.
You gave Seokhyeon
a drink with a heart on it.
What?
[sighs]
So you saw it.
Yeah, I'm happy these days.
I'm really glad to hear that.
Yeah, so let's both live happy lives.
[♪ music fades]
CHEMICAL AND BIOLOGICAL ENGINEERING
PROFESSOR SUNWOO SEOK
[sighs]
May I help you?
Oh. I'm here to see Professor Sunwoo.
[assistant] Ah.
He's gone to the president's office.
-May I ask what you're here for?
-[hesitates]
We're family.
-If he's not here--
-He'll probably be back soon.
Why don't you wait inside?
Ah…
[sighs softly]
[♪ pensive music playing]
-[knocks on door]
-[door opens]
He's taking a while.
Should I try calling him?
No, I'll just go.
[hesitates] Would it be okay
to leave this here?
Sure, go ahead.
[♪ music fades]
[door closes]
KOREA SCIENCE UNIVERSITY
Let me keep this, Dad.
-[young Chan gasps]
-[door slams]
[♪ sentimental music playing]
How long are you going to keep doing this?
What more do I have to do
to make you stop?
[sighs heavily]
[sniffles]
[♪ music fades]
Excuse me, you said you're family.
Are you his son who's working
as an animator in the US?
You are, right?
I heard a lot about you
from Professor Sunwoo.
He always rushes to see
any movies that get released.
He even buys tickets for his students.
[♪ slow instrumental music
playing on speakers]
[Haran clears throat]
[Haran clears throat loudly]
Can I ask you something, sir?
I heard there's a famous bakery nearby.
Do you know where it is?
-Excuse me?
-[chuckles softly]
I came here to buy bread.
I heard there's
a really famous bakery here.
[sighs] You're such a bad liar.
Were you worried
something would've happened again?
Well…
I also came to check
Daejeon's fashion trends.
[gasps] Wow.
Everyone's so fashionable here.
And I thought that if anything happened,
I could give you a hug.
[inhales sharply] Look at you.
When going to Gyeongju,
at the airport, and now Daejeon…
You keep surprising me like this.
You'll make me get my hopes up.
I'll keep thinking you'll appear anywhere.
Fine.
I'll appear anywhere you are,
so you can get your hopes up.
[man] Seonu Chan!
[assistant] I'm so glad you've recovered.
Professor Sunwoo gave up on his research
just before presenting it
to go take care of you in America
when you were badly injured.
[doctor in English]
We've done everything we can.
Now we just have to hope
that he'll pull through.
The truth is, you should be aware
it's not very likely that he'll wake up.
[♪ emotional music playing]
[♪ emotional music continuing]
[in Korean] Thanks…
for the watch.
[sighs]
[exhales nervously]
Maybe you should return your degree.
A famous engineering professor
can't even fix a broken watch?
It's working well now.
Thank you…
for fixing it.
If you're grateful,
you can pay me back later.
[♪ music continues]
[♪ music ends]
Grandma called.
She thanked me and said I did well.
[Haran] Really?
That's great.
I'm so glad you gave it back to him.
That watch must be
dozens of times more precious now.
It could have ended
with him being sad about losing it,
but now, it's the watch that his son
fixed and returned to him.
Can I see you for a moment again?
[♪ relaxing music playing on speakers]
Huh?
How did you…
Remember when we went to that restaurant?
When I was in bad shape because of my ear.
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[groans]
[server yelps]
It's noisy in there.
I'll go bring our stuff.
It must have gotten mixed up
in my stuff back then.
I found it
when I unpacked my luggage here.
Ah…
I don't need it anymore, though.
I'm already using a different one.
Plus, I have dozens of pens now.
Someone gave me a whole bunch
as a gift. [chuckles softly]
That's why I'm giving it back now.
I…
was worried that I'd remind you
of the memories back then.
But I thought you wouldn't be wavered now.
Just think of it as a pen
that's the most effective and use it.
I know how important it is
to have a tool that fits you just right
since I'm an animator.
I can just get used to this pen.
Let me borrow this for a second.
[♪ pleasant song playing]
[pen scraping]
[breathes deeply]
Just consider this pen
a pen that I found for you,
not a pen that you got as a gift
or a pen that made you sad
when you lost it.
And… here's a lucky charm.
You know you'll get lucky
once you see an iridescent cloud.
You can see one every day now,
so you'll be lucky every day.
[chuckles softly]
-[sighs]
-[inhales sharply, grunts]
Just use it.
I sincerely want you to use it again.
All right.
I will.
It's the pen you found for me now.
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
[exclaims] Really?
[exclaims softly] All right.
Thank you. Okay.
[sighs]
No way.
-This is crazy.
-What is it?
Something good really happened.
I'm receiving an award.
The Best Designer Award
at the Fashion Awards.
See? I told you that you'd be lucky.
-[chuckles softly]
-Congratulations.
[♪ song fades]
[Manjae] Genius.
Are you here?
Huh?
Hey, Genius.
[Genius barks]
Is there something there?
[Manjae exclaims] What…
Nabong!
[♪ somber music playing]
What are you doing here at this hour?
Hey, Manjae.
I wanted to get a cup of coffee
after I finished work,
but I didn't realize it was so late.
The snow was beautiful,
so I was watching it for a bit.
-[♪ music fades]
-It's so late…
And you're dressed so lightly.
It's cold.
Come on, let's go inside.
Get yourself warmed up.
What on earth is going on?
I was so absorbed in work,
I didn't notice the time.
You know how focused I can get.
Are you sure nothing's wrong?
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
Is everything really okay?
Is this some trending challenge?
Why is everyone asking me that? [chuckles]
Did I neglect my skincare
because I was too busy?
Have some warm tea.
[sighs]
[Manjae] What on earth
is going on with you?
[♪ music ends]
[♪ upbeat music playing on speakers]
LAUNDRY DETERGENT
LAVENDER
[woman] Aren't you my Hadam?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
It's me.
Mom.
Mom?
-Oh, my goodness!
-[♪ music fades]
I finally got to meet you.
I wanted to see you so much.
It's me, Yougyum's mom.
What? Ah…
Ah!
Hello.
[Yougyum's mom]
Goodness, it's so nice to meet you.
I recognized you right away.
Our house is plastered with photos of you.
-[chuckles awkwardly]
-I feel like I'm meeting a celebrity.
If it's all right, could I give you a hug?
[chuckling] My dear Hadam.
It's so nice to see you.
[♪ emotional music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[whimpering]
[Yougyum's mom] What's wrong? What is it?
[Hyewon] ♪ Sleep well, dear Hadam ♪
♪ Sleep in Mommy's arms ♪
♪ Sleep well, dear Hadam ♪
♪ Sleep tight ♪
I found…
Mom's smell.
[Hadam crying]
-[stomach rumbles]
-[gasps]
[laughing]
Come on. I'll make you a meal.
[laughing] Let's go.
[man in English] Excuse me.
Where is the grocery store?
-[steam hissing]
-[♪ music fades]
[chuckles] Excuse me.
Where is the grocery store?
-[Yougyum's mom in Korean] Honey.
-Come on in.
[chuckling]
Hello.
Look who it is!
Isn't she our superstar?
-Our dear Hadam.
-Ah…
We told Yougyum to bring you,
but he said
we shouldn't bother your studies
and kept you hidden all along.
I ran into her by chance
at the supermarket.
Welcome.
Did you eat?
Join us for a meal.
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
Gosh. I told you to bring me
when you're buying heavy stuff.
I'll bring these upstairs. [chuckles]
-[thuds]
-[groans] Gosh!
My goodness.
[Yougyum's mom and Hadam chuckle]
[Hadam exclaims] I can't believe him.
LET'S BE SOMEONE HADAM WILL BE PROUD OF!
[Yougyum's mom] I wondered why
he only got perfect scores in English.
I heard you told him in your first year.
The Major League?
If that's your goal,
shouldn't you at least
study English in advance?
[in English] I want to be better
than I was yesterday.
"Challenge."
[in Korean] Challenge.
[Yougyum's mom] Since then,
his father has been studying English, too.
He said he wants to help Yougyum.
This is how much influence
you have over our family.
[chuckles shyly]
[♪ music fades]
He's unbelievable.
[Yougyum's dad]
Honey, should I braise the fish?
Hang on.
-Sorry. Take a look around.
-Okay.
[Yougyum's mom]
But how did you end up dating Yougyum?
He said he had a crush on you
since elementary school.
[Hadam] Thinking back,
he was the only one who understood me.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
[kid 1] Why aren't your parents
here for the field day?
[kid 2] Hey, she's the poor kid
whose parents both died.
[kid 1] Really? That's so pitiful.
Hey, having your parents
pass away isn't pitiful.
It's just sad.
[Hadam groans]
I solved this when I stayed up
studying last night.
Hadam.
In baseball, throwing pull power
every time will strain your body.
You need a breather to grow stronger.
A breather?
That's why…
you need a breather now.
All right. Pitcher Cha Yougyum
is ready to throw.
-[Yougyum groans]
-[sighs]
[both exclaim excitedly]
I hit it!
Run, Hadam!
Go!
[♪ pleasant music playing]
Right.
Yougyum always understood me.
-[♪ music ends]
-[cell phone buzzes]
[Manjae] Nabong, guess what I found?
[gasps softly]
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
Manjae, where did you get that photo?
Oh. [chuckles]
I was organizing my vinyl collection,
-and it just fell out.
-[Nana gasps on phone]
I can't believe it.
That was such a long time ago.
I wonder if that tree is still there.
Remember the tteokbokki place
we used to go to in the market?
What was it called?
-Ah! Fat Tteokbokki.
-Fat Tteokbokki.
-[Manjae] Right?
-[laughs]
[laughs]
Ah… I'm craving
that super sweet tteokbokki.
Do you want to go
have tteokbokki this evening?
[hesitates] No…
You shouldn't ditch work, right?
Come on.
Nabong, have you forgotten
that I'm the owner?
I can totally ditch work.
[♪ music fades]
Well, well.
I caught you. Are you ditching work?
No, I'm receiving an award.
Oh, right. The Fashion Awards is today.
-Congratulations.
-[chuckles softly]
See you.
[♪ heart-fluttering music playing]
[footsteps echoing]
[Raemee exclaims] Love.
That means you like him too.
[Hayeong] No way.
Was he right?
Why does he look so cool
when he's just walking?
[suit rustle echoes]
Why am I blushing?
And why am I sweating?
Are you free this evening?
[Hayeong] This evening?
Not morning or afternoon?
Is he asking me out?
[gasps inwardly] On a date?
I got a reply that the factory
couldn't get any of the bio silk
you talked about.
I did more research
and got in touch with an industry
tech reporter who wrote about it.
We're meeting this evening.
We may find a way to do it.
[Hayeong] Mr. Yeon's cheeks
seem a little red, too.
Huh? And he's sweating.
Was Raemee really right?
Then we really like each other?
[clinking]
Great job with the meeting.
How about some wine?
Just you and me,
alone.
Sure. I'd like that.
Pardon? Uh…
Are you saying you'll come?
[♪ music fades]
Ah.
Yes, I'm free.
I'll drive, then.
I'll see you at the parking lot
at 7:00 p.m.
[sighs]
Why are we meeting at 7:00 p.m.?
Right.
The new material.
The meeting.
GYUM'S LAUNDRY
[Yougyum] I'm home.
Mom.
Mom, I must have lost my mind.
I miss Hadam so much,
I must be hallucinating.
But… [breathing shakily]
it's still so nice to see her.
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
[Yougyum sniffles]
You idiot.
It's really me.
Wow.
She's even talking now.
I must have gone crazy
from missing her so much.
You idiot.
It really is me.
[stuttering] Is it really you?
You're really Hadam?
I didn't give Seokhyeon my number.
Someone left a drink at my seat
with a heart post-it,
and I rushed out thinking it was from you.
When I heard it was from Seokhyeon,
I gave it back to him.
Really?
I'm sorry I misunderstood.
I wasn't having fun at karaoke either.
My friends took me there to comfort me,
but I just kept crying
at the thought of you.
I'm sorry I misunderstood you, too.
But why are you wearing glasses?
Has your eyesight gotten bad?
No,
I don't need them now.
And you? Why were you
at the nurse's office? Were you sick?
[breathing shakily]
I just got a small cut on my hand,
-but I'm all better now.
-[sniffling]
[both crying]
I'm sorry, Hadam.
[crying] I'm more sorry.
[Yougyum] I missed you so much.
[Hadam] I missed you even more.
-[♪ grandiose music playing on speakers]
-[announcer] The Best Designer Award.
-Nana Atelier, Song Haran.
-[applause]
There are two winners this year.
-Onne Apparel, Kang Eunchan.
-[cameras clicking]
[applause]
[♪ music fades]
[Eunchan] Haran.
I have to go to the factory.
There's a fabric issue.
I booked a table at Haeon,
the restaurant nearby.
Take this and go there.
I said I'd buy dinner for my brother,
but I can't let him eat alone.
Sorry, but just have dinner
with him, okay?
-♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-[clapping]
-[♪ pleasant music playing]
-♪ Happy birthday… ♪
-[yawns]
-[chuckles]
I'm sorry. I haven't slept
for the past three days.
Sorry. Right.
♪ Happy birthday, dear… ♪
Kang Hyeokchan.
♪ Kang Hyeokchan ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[cheers]
A Mr. Kang from our house
asked me to give it to you.
-What?
-Good luck.
VITAMINS FOR ENERGY
A CUSHION FOR A NAP
CHOCOLATE AFTER LUNCH
CHAMOMILE AFTER WORK
WITH THESE, YOU CAN SLEEP BETTER
[chuckles softly]
[kisses, chuckles]
-I love you.
-Hmm?
That's so sudden.
-[scoffs]
-[cell phone vibrating]
[sighs wearily]
It's work.
Good luck with the embassy interview.
Hello?
[sighs] I can't believe I have to work
when you're leaving.
I'm so sorry, Chan.
It's fine.
I told you I won't get upset
about you being busy.
I'll be back during vacation. I love you.
I'm so sorry.
Leave me a message when you arrive.
[cell phone pings]
[Hyeokchan] I can't go back to Korea
because of my lab schedule.
And my phone's broken,
so I won't be able to text for a while.
Leave me a message
if there's anything urgent.
[Hayeong] I knew it.
Are you sure he just doesn't want to come?
-What?
-Well, I haven't seen it myself,
but he was so nice to you
when he was in Seoul.
But you were always busy
and didn't keep in touch often.
You didn't even show much affection.
You'll get dumped at this rate.
[sighs] You're right.
I guess I deserve it.
That's too bad.
What's that reaction?
Do you even like Hyeokchan?
Of course I do. He's my boyfriend.
[Hayeong] No, not like that.
Do you love him?
[Haran] Mmm?
[Eunchan] Did Chan send that?
He sent a drawing pen
for his designer girlfriend?
Wow. And even with your name
engraved on it?
[Haran] But how did you come up
with the idea of sending me a pen?
[♪ sentimental music playing]
I KEPT THINKING ABOUT HOW YOU SAID
YOU FELT LIKE YOU WERE TRAPPED
I GUESS I WANTED THAT PEN
TO BE THAT "IF" FOR YOU
[sighs]
Chan understands me so well…
SORRY, I WAS RAMBLING
I miss you, Hyeokchan.
Ta-da! I'm at the airport!
I wanted to tell you something in person.
Chan. I love you.
I love you, Chan. [chuckles]
[Eunchan] Haran, what do I do?
Chan…
-Hyeokchan is dead.
-[siren blaring]
-[♪ music fades]
-[applause]
[Eunchan] I moved to Onne Apparel.
It's awkward giving you my business card.
Have you been well?
It's already been…
seven years.
I always wondered how you were doing,
but I felt too guilty to contact you.
Why would you feel guilty?
-What is it?
-Oh…
Were you getting checkups here?
Huh?
Ahh.
I was at a different ER
when I collapsed last time.
[chuckles]
I got a referral, so I come here.
It's closer.
-What is it?
-Ah…
I got treated here before.
[chuckles softly]
I'll go ask where we can get the results.
We have to go to the annex.
Really?
But why are you dressed up today?
[Manjae] Hmm?
I have to be dressed up
to go somewhere later.
-[inhales sharply] Mmm…
-[Manjae chuckles]
[Chan] Where are you going?
[automation] The door is closing.
[automation in English]
The door is closing.
[metallic clinking]
[elevator dings]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[in Korean] Huh? Hey, roomie!
[pants]
[metallic clinking echoes]
[metallic clinking]
-[cell phone vibrating]
-[panting]
Mr. Park.
Sorry, I'll head over there.
Okay.
[professor] Visiting neurology resident
from Boston General Hospital,
Cha Sujin.
I'm Cha Sujin.
I'll do my best
to learn as much as I can here.
-Nice to meet you all.
-[applause]
[doctor] Dr. Cha.
You shouldn't wear accessories here.
Sorry. I forgot to take it off.
MEDICAL STAFF SEARCH
LEE SUJIN
[Chan] I'm sure she was in a gown.
[breathes deeply]
[♪ music fades]
All right.
I got the results. [chuckles]
-[inhales deeply]
-But why did you suddenly get off earlier?
Oh. It was nothing.
There's a convenience store nearby.
I'll go buy some drinks for the nurses.
-[Manjae] Mmm.
-[plastic rustling]
Hmm? They didn't say it was going to rain.
Is it a shower?
I have a hood, so it's fine.
I'll be back soon.
[Manjae] Okay.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[Sujin] Who's that? Your friend?
[Hyeokchan] No, just my roommate.
Dr. Cha, we're starting rounds.
[Sujin] Okay.
[Haran] Hospitalized?
-Hyeokchan?
-[Eunchan] Don't you remember?
He hurt his hand badly in the lab.
He even got surgery.
A surgery?
I never heard anything about that.
[♪ music fades]
-[Nana exclaims excitedly]
-[Manjae chuckles]
Manjae, what do you think?
[exclaims] It looks like
Genius' paw print. It's cute.
-Right?
-Should I buy it for you?
-Sure.
-Okay. How much is it?
-Manjae!
-What? What is it?
Tteokbokki! Tteokbokki!
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
[hums delightedly]
[chuckles] It's good.
Having tteokbokki after ditching
is the best.
Right?
That only applies
to the Chuncheon fashionista Nabong.
I never ditched school.
Ah. Right, of course.
You were the bookworm Park Manjae.
That's right.
[both laugh]
Excuse me.
Are you Kim Nana, by any chance?
It seems like it, right?
We're fashion design majors,
and we're huge fans.
Could I have an autograph?
Mmm… Oh, dear. My face is my autograph.
You can take a selfie with me.
-One, two, three.
-[camera clicks]
[student 1] Thank you.
By the way, your husband is freaking…
[student 2] I mean, he's really cool.
-No, I'm…
-He's freaking cool, isn't he?
I care about looks.
[students and Nana laugh]
[♪ music fades]
[Hayeong] Why do I feel so nervous
being alone with him?
Oh… I feel so hot.
Should I turn off the heater?
Would it show that I'm nervous?
-[window whirring]
-[groans] It's hot.
[breathes deeply]
[coughing]
[sniffles, clears throat]
Should I close the window?
No, it's fine. You can do as you like.
[whirring]
Then would it be possible to get samples?
Yes, but it's over five times
the price of silk,
and the durability tests
aren't stable yet.
That's why I want to try this.
I want to make clothes
not just for display
but to prove the future.
I really want to achieve that
for our brand.
You seem very determined.
How should we get the samples?
There's a research facility
I came in touch with.
It's a bio startup company.
I'll give you their number.
-Really?
-[reporter] Yes.
And I'll ask them again
for their cooperation.
Thank you… [groans, chuckles excitedly]
I was just so grateful.
-Are you all right? [laughs]
-[Hayeong] Yes.
-You really mean it?
-Of course.
-Ms. Song, here's my business card.
-Ah.
Contact me if you have any questions.
Thank you.
It was nice seeing you again, Taeseok.
What? Do you two know each other?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm actually his junior from college.
He asked me
to keep it a secret
in case you felt uneasy.
I tried to get close to him,
but he never let me back then.
And now--
Thank you for today, Mr. Chae.
I'll see you next time.
You haven't changed a bit.
I'd like to get to know you better.
How about a glass of wine together?
Just the two of us.
Just the two of us?
That's okay, right?
I don't think it's my place
to say yes or no.
Then excuse me.
[Hayeong] What was that?
Did he just set me up on a date?
Didn't he have feelings for me?
Mr. Yeon.
Is it really okay for me
to have a drink with him, alone?
Why are you asking me that?
I think it's your business.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
Ah. Fine.
Mr. Chae, let's go have some wine.
I'm really craving a drink today.
[sighs]
-[sighs]
-[♪ music fades]
[Yougyum's mom] Hadam, enjoy these dishes.
You even packed side dishes for me?
Thank you.
Make sure to visit after the CSAT.
I promise I will.
But could you give me
one more hug?
Of course, I can. Come here.
[chuckles]
-[♪ amusing music playing]
-[Yougyum's mom exclaims]
I'll see you again later. Hmm?
Okay.
-Me too. I want a hug, too.
-My goodness!
[exclaims] Then I should join as well.
[all laughing]
[Haran] A surgery?
I never heard anything about that.
[Eunchan] You didn't know?
I guess Chan didn't tell you
in case you got worried.
[Chan clears throat] Excuse me.
You're Designer Song Haran
who won the Best Designer Award, right?
[chuckles] Oh? How are you here?
I have a habit of congratulating people
who receive awards.
Here.
Congratulations.
[♪ uplifting song playing]
Thanks.
[inhales sharply]
But why do you look so down
when you just won an award?
No, I'm really happy.
No, your expression looks…
-like this.
-[chuckles]
[chuckles softly] Let's go.
Go where?
Photos? That's so random.
I told you, what you took doesn't count.
Oh. This one's good.
All right. Come here.
Our Best Designer.
Okay. One, two, three.
You should smile.
This time with the flowers.
Here. Smile.
All right. One, two, three.
I'll do an ugly face for you
to make you look prettier.
One, two, three. [hums teasingly]
[Haran chuckles]
[Chan chuckles]
Pretty pose. [sneezes]
[Haran] Look at your expressions.
[giggles]
-Let's go to our next course.
-What?
Where? Where are we going?
Come on, let's go.
This way.
Wow. You came to such
a nice place alone? Tsk.
You're the one
who disappeared without telling me.
Excuse me, could you take a picture of us?
Sure, of course.
-Two, three.
-[camera clicks]
-Thank you.
-[Chan] Thank you.
Would you like a photo, too?
Sure.
Okay. Smile. [clears throat]
It'll look nice
if you smile at each other.
-Can you look at each other?
-Like this?
What should I do?
-[Chan] I'll do an ugly face for you.
-[chuckles]
-We'll take one for you, too.
-Oh, I'm okay.
[mouthing] Thank you.
[man] I'll take it now.
One, two, three.
[♪ song fades]
[Hadam] There's a blanket I've been using
since I was a baby,
and it had this distinctive scent.
It felt warm and comforting
and made me feel like I'm going to cry.
But that scent disappeared.
It smelled just like my mom used to.
But when your mom hugged me earlier,
I smelled the same scent.
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
[chuckles softly]
So I ended up crying.
I thought it was the smell of detergent,
but I guess that was the scent of a mom.
Oh? Then wouldn't I smell similar?
Try smelling me.
[Hadam sniffs]
[both laugh]
You have a different scent.
I'm going to marry you, no matter what.
What?
[chuckles] Whenever I see you,
I wonder how you could be so wonderful.
But I understood when I saw your parents.
If they become my family,
I'll be so happy.
Still, I'll love you the most.
What do I do?
[sighs] I'm so happy,
I feel like I'm going to faint.
[chuckles] There's nothing left
but happiness for us.
Mm.
Let's go. I want to study.
Okay.
The minimum CSAT requirement?
It's going to be a piece of cake.
Why aren't you coming?
-[♪ music fades]
-[Hadam giggles]
Did you really faint?
Come on. Stop fooling around.
[breath trembling] Hadam, what do I do?
I can't get up.
My foot…
What?
[♪ tense music playing]
-[winces]
-Huh?
[stutters] Yougyum…
[♪ music fades]
Thank you for the umbrella.
[both chuckle]
See you.
-[in English] Yes!
-[in Korean] Bye.
Sure. Bye.
-Bye.
-Get home safely.
Okay.
Tsk. He made me
get my hopes up for nothing.
I should thank him.
I'm so grateful that he introduced us.
[line connects, rings]
Why isn't he picking up?
Mr. Yeon, I had so much fun
with Mr. Chae today…
What are you spying on?
Gosh, you scared me.
Did Mr. Yeon not come back here
after the meeting?
He just dropped by for a bit and left.
Ah.
You'd better buy me lunch…
[in singsong] for the information.
He always gets off work late, though.
[deliveryman] Mr. Yeon Taeseok?
There's a delivery for you.
I'll take that.
Thank you.
YEON TAESEOK
Mr. Yeon.
What? He's not home, either?
Mr. Yeon, I…
Oh?
[♪ somber music playing]
What…
-What's going on?
-[breath trembling]
[♪ music fades]
[exclaims delightedly]
This keychain is so cute. [chuckles]
Manjae, let's go have sujebi next time.
And let's visit Chuncheon as well
before it gets colder.
-Let's…
-Kim Nabong.
What?
Why aren't you coming?
You.
Where are you going this time?
I said let's go to Chuncheon.
You're behaving just like back then.
When you suddenly left for France
when you were 20,
you acted just like this.
You called me out of the blue
and said, "Let's do this. Let's go here."
Then you suddenly disappeared
without saying anything.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
That was a long time ago. Don't be silly.
Tell me.
What is it this time?
What on earth is going on with you?
[Haran chuckles softly]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
Yes. May I ask who's calling?
Oh…
All right.
I'll go and check.
[♪ music fades]
[grunts, inhales sharply] Ah.
[hums]
[sighs] I miss you already.
[chuckles softly]
[cell phone buzzes, chimes]
-Hmm?
-[Haran] Can you come out for a bit?
[pants] That was fast, wasn't it?
Aren't you tired?
I mean, I told you to go home and rest,
but…
I was actually really sad
that you left. [chuckles]
[♪ tense music playing]
What is it?
Is something wrong?
I just got a call from the restaurant.
What restaurant?
[♪ music intensifies]
I think you owe me an explanation.
[high-pitched ringing]
[♪ music fades]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[♪ emotional song playing]
[Haran] It sounds like
they're not meant to be together.
[Chan] Can you tell me what you know
about what happened seven years ago?
I'll tell her everything
and apologize to her.
[Taeseok] The chance
of Ms. Song and I dating is zero.
[Hayeong] Am I really just mistaken
about all those situations?
[Nana] It's rare to find
someone who makes you smile.
[Haran crying] What if you're not okay?
What if something else happens?
[Chan] I want to stay by her side,
but I don't know what to do.
[♪ song fades]
[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park